Nguyen Huu Duy

https://www.linkedin.com/in/huuduynvc

**SUMMARY** 

I have a passion for programming. I like to create something useful for the community or myself by everything learned. After more than 2 years working as a backend developer, I have grown valuable experience in designing server-side applications with NodeJS/NestJS, ExpressJS, GraphQL and other tech stacks. I believe I can quickly adapt to your team; make a long-term and real impact on your ongoing projects with my skills and experience.

#### **EDUCATION**

## VNUHCM - University Of Science

Bachelor of Software Engineering; GPA 8.1/10

Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam Jun 2017 - May 2022

Mobile: +84-369-439-969

Email: nguyenhuuduynvc@gmail.com

**EXPERIENCE** 

Codelight

Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam Backend Engineer · *Jun* 2022 - Sep 2023

o Develop and maintain server-side applications: Create and maintain scalable and efficient server-side applications using NodeJS/NestJS and related technologies such as GraphQL, MongoDB, PostgresSQL, Redis...

- o Design and implement APIs/GraphQL: Design and implement RESTful APIs/GraphQL that can be consumed by front-end developers.
- o Deploy and manage applications: Deploy and manage server-side applications on Google Cloud Platform.
- o Implement security measures: Implement security measures such as encryption and authentication to protect sensitive data and prevent unauthorized access.

Freelance

Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam May 2021 - Jul 2022

Software Engineer ·

o Develop personal projects: Develop personal projects such as attendance plugin for Moodle, e-learning website, classroom management website using HTML, CSS, Javascript, NodeJs/PHP.

Mpire Agency

Software Engineering Intern ·

Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

o Develop applications: Write PHP code with Phalcon framework and SEO improvement for website

### **PROJECTS**

#### Heydevs (https://heydevs.io)

Backend Engineer · Team size: 10+

Customer: Codelight Apr 2023 - Sep 2023

Description: HeyDevs is the active sourcing platform in the APAC region.

My responsibilities:

• Develope GraphQL and RESTful APIs using NestJS, Express and PostgesSQL.

• Responsible for handling the email/notification service using Novu, AWS SES, Brevo, and FCM.

Technologies used: NodeJS/NestJS, GraphQL, PostgresSQL, Redis, Websocket

#### EZ Wallet (https://ezwallet.xyz)

Backend Engineer · Team size: 5

Customer: Codelight Nov 2022 - Apr 2023

Description: EZ Wallet is the crypto wallet for Defi, Web3 Dapps and NFTs.

My responsibilities:

- o Design database and user authentication mechanism to manage data for the learn and earn feature.
- o Integrate the buying/selling of crypto with fiat currency through MoonPay/Transak.
- Develop a real-time chat feature using WebSocket and Socket.io.

- o Develop a notification service using FCM.
- Write, deploy, and airdrop an NFT smart contract using Hardhat.

Technologies used: NodeJS/NestJS, PostgresSQL, Redis, Websocket

# Warena (https://warena.io)

Backend Engineer · Team size: 6

Customer: Codelight Jun 2022 - Dec 2022

Description: Warena is the first personalized and play-to-earn nonfungible token (NFT) metaverse game, has raised over \$1.5 million.

My responsibilities:

o Maintain and develop of features: buying/selling items, handling the NFT deposit/withdrawal process in-game to prevent cheating, in-game item trading, weapon upgrades, and an item farming system

o Refactor code support multi-chain (BSC, Thunder Core, Harmony One).

Technologies used: NodeJS/NestJS, GraphQL, MongoDB

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Backend: NodeJS, NestJS, ExpressJS, GraphQL

Blockchain: Solidity, Hardhat

Database: PostgresSQL, Mysql, MongoDB
Others: Docker, Agile/Scrum, Microservices, Git, ...